A train in my mind now, a train in my mind
Running so fast to unknown direction now
Its heart is beating in mine now
Its heart is beating in mine
And always the same house on the window
I'm getting away now, I'm getting away
But always the same place
Meeting my face
Trampling on time's face, trampling on time
But I know my birthday wasn't mine no
Power fighting with light yell
Power fighting with light
Seasons destroying my memory power again
Trampling on time's face, trampling on time
But I know my birthday wasn't mine, no
Power fighting with light yell
Power fighting with light
Seasons destroying my memory power again